2017-08-08
	* Passport Panel: When adding an extra scan, Check whether the user have clicked the Add button and give a warning if not.
	* Replace Latest Changes sidebar with a collapsable "Help & Latest Changes" sidebar visible on all panels. PDF-files could be used to display each help chapter?
	* Change arrow icon to a hoverable "i" (info) icon, displaying a ballon tooltip with Remarks from profile page. For persons with no remarks the icon can be hidden.

2017-08-07
	* TM30 Panel::Saved Printouts TM 30: Show small table under this tab for Missing TM 30 Printouts with these criteria:
		1. Persons in Thailand missing TM 30 Printout
		2. Persons in Thailand whose last arrival date is later than TM 30 notification date.

2017-08-05
	* Add these to ChangeLog default entries.
		"Updated Documents Stock."
		"Changed status from Abroad to Thailand for K. XYZ."
		"Changed status to Abroad for K. XYZ."
	* Add Separate table for Tourist visas on due tasks. Check visa type and visa extension in db.
	
			[Monastic]	[Due Date]	[WD]	[Remaining Time]	[30 Day Extension - Immigration]
			PersonOne	27/02/2017	WED 	21 Days				Already Extended (red color)
			PersonTwo	17/04/2017	SAT		14 Days				17/03/2017		
			
2017-05-15
	* Passport panel: After Archiving Departure Card Scan, the Departure Card Scan button is still inactive.

2017-04-01
	* Monastery panel: when saving address data for monastery, whether adding new data or editing old data, all address data for that monastery disappears.
	* Due Tasks panel: Passport renewal on both tabs, and Visa Extensions table on abroad tab shows with scroll bars and hides the last line, the table should be expanding below to show all lines.

2017-03-14
	* Passport panel: when there is only one existing scan, clicking the preview button gives an error message "error to generate pdf".

2017-02-15
	* TM 30 Panel: When registering TM30 old entries remain in list of saved printouts.
	* TM 30 Panel: If two or more monastics are reported in person at office on same date, there will be two separate printouts for that date, which the system currently does not support.

2017-02-06
	* Prawat: New version of form. Changed answers for dhamma studies. Optional answers for patimokkha chanters are included in separate file.
	* Prawat: Fields values to change for patimokkha chanters: dhammaStudiesThaiPDF2 and studiesLastYearActivitiesThaiPDF3. 

2017-01-24
	* Passport panel: when archiving passport it gives a message that the Departure card has been archived successfully.

2017-01-08
	* Add/Change Visa: When clearing a visa, all extensions should also be cleared. But the extensions still remain on the Visa Extension Panel.


2017-01-01
	* Maybe adjust tab order of some fields as below. 

Monastic Profile:
Nickname, Name, Middle Name, Last Name, Mother, Father
Birth Country, Birth Place, Ethnicity, Nationality
Occupation, Occupation (Thai), Certificate, Certificate (Thai)
Previous Residence Country, Residence Wat, Adviser's name, Adviser's Wat

Passport:
Pspt. Country, Issued at
Port of Entry, First Entry

90 Day notice - online notification:
Given Name, Middle Name, DoB, Nationality, TM6 Number, Arrived in Thailand, By Transportation, Type of Housing, Building Name


2016-12-28

Perhaps the new db fields can be arranged like this? (9 fields)


DOCUMENTS FOR SAMNAK PUT

1. Prawat
	Printed
	Signed by abbot
	Sent to Jao Kana Ampher & Jangwat
	Signed by Jao Kana Ampher & Jangwat

2. Extension Request Letter (Samnak Put)
	Printed
	Signed by abbot

3. Passport photocopy (refer to "Signed photocopies" field that is used for the document stock panel)
   BaiSuddhi photocopy (refer to "Signed photocopies" that is used for the document stock panel)
	Printed
	Signed by monastic

4. ---> Samnak Put
	Sent
	Signed by Puu Wah


DOCUMENTS FOR IMMIGRATION

Approval Letter from Samnak Put (add checkbox for this and check whether "Samnak Put" field has the status "Signed by Puu Wah" or not.

5. TM. 7 (Signed by monastic)
	Printed
	Photo attached

6. Extension Request Letter (Immigration)
	Printed
	Signed by abbot

7. Passport photocopy (Signed by monastic)
   BaiSuddhi photocopy (Signed by monastic)
	Printed

Maybe the following three can be kept together in one db field?
8. Overstay form (Signed by monastic)
   Acknowledgement form (Signed by monastic)
   TM. 30 Printout
	Printed

 ---> Immigration
	Visa Extension Approved

-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

2016-12-26
	* Due Tasks: some weekdays other than Sat/Sun are showing up in red color.
	* Due Tasks: Passport Renewal both Thailand & Abroad tabs, remaining time is not showing remaining months and is thus inaccurate. Example: 
		K. Raryel - Due Date 26/02/2018 - Remaining time 1 year(s) - should say 1 year(s) 2 month(s).
		K. Fredrik - Due Date 23/12/2020 - Remaining time 3 year(s) 27 day(s) - should say 3 year(s) 11 month(s) 27 day(s).
		K. Sindre - Due Date 03/06/2019 - Remaining time 2 year(s) 8 day(s) - should say 2 year(s) 5 month(s) 8 day(s).

2016-12-24
	* Monastic Profile: Perhaps change the title of "Occupation/Certificate" to "Occupation/Education".

2016-12-23
	* Printed Documents Stock: When setting values for Signed 90 day forms and Printed photos, values are stored properly in db, but if Printed Photos is set to 0 both Printed photos and Signed 90 day forms is showing as "MISSING". 
	* Signed 90 Day Forms is showing as "0" instead of "MISSING" if it is set to 0 and Printed Photos is set to more than 0. 
	* Printed Documents Stock: when changing value for Signed Photocopies, save button doesn't become active.
	* Printed Documents Stock: K.Stuart and K.Adrian shows up first in the list for some reason, the remaining monastics are shown in correct seniority order.
	* Add Changelog Entry: "Updated Monastery Data" should be boolean (checkbox?) instead of the list of monastics.

2016-12-21
	* Saved Printouts TM 30: Monastics column is not wide enough to show all names.
	* Monastic Profile (Dhamma Studies): Save button doesn't activate when editing this field.
	* Due Tasks (90 Day Notice/Visa Extension table): Remaining Time column is not wide enough.
	* Change log viewer: Perhaps wrap text of Recent Changes in Due Tasks to avoid horizontal scroll bar?
	* Change log viewer: What do you think of these tabbing formats for viewing Optional Comments? To me the bottom one looks better.

2016-12-21 13:57:55 K. Fredrik:
       	 Updated Monastic Profile Data for XYZ.
	 Remark:
	 First remark line.
	 Second remark line.
	 Third remark line.

or

2016-12-21 13:57:55 K. Fredrik:
         Updated Monastic Profile Data for XYZ.
	 Remark: First remark line.
	 	 Second remark line.
	 	 Third remark line.